{
    "subject": "resource/Sergey_Vasilyevich_Gerasimov",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "Russian artist",
    "human_readable": "Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov is a Russian artist.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.98870849609375,
            "question": "Is Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov a Russian artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9251364469528198,
            "question": "Are there any famous paintings by Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.898288905620575,
            "question": "What nationality is Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8703142404556274,
            "question": "Where is Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8351524472236633,
            "question": "What profession does Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7901220917701721,
            "question": "What country is associated with Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.560067892074585,
            "question": "What period in history did Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov work in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5543323755264282,
            "question": "Can you name some famous Russian artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33357471227645874,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of Russian art?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21245521306991577,
            "question": "What are some influential factors in Russian art?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov is a Russian artist.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1373_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of Russian art?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1373_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name some famous Russian artists?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1373_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What period in history did Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov work in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1373_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1373_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1373_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1373_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1373_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1373_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1373_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1373_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1373_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1373_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1373_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all five documents contain information that confirms Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov was indeed a Soviet and/or Russian painter, as stated in the query. The various descriptions of his work, education, and affiliations (e.g., student of Konstantin Korovin, member of the Makovets group, teacher at Vkhutemas) all suggest that he had a connection to Russia or the Soviet Union."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references to Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov being a Soviet and Russian painter, which supports the statement that he is a Russian artist."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}